makeameme.org 2018-10-04

# Make a Meme Privacy Policy

We are committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy statement explains data collection and use practices of the makeameme.org site (the Site) By accessing the Site, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this privacy statement.

### Collecting Your Personal Information

Personal information may be collected when: 

  * You provide information when using the 'contact us' form.
  * You provide information when using the 'report' option.
  * You register for an account, either via our website or one of our replated apps. 
  * We may ask for your email address for purposes of validating a user as being authentic and for strictly non-promotional notifications. 

### Storage of Information

Information is stored on secured internet servers that only we have access to and can only be connected to via encrypted connection. 

Created images can only be viewed by the creator of the image and persons that the user choosees to share it with - via direct image saving or sharing the unique URL for that creation, unless the user chooses to make a meme 'public', in which case it will be linked to from the '/newest' page (at makeameme.org/newest) for a limited time. 

### Use of Information

We use information solely for the purpose of tracking ownership of created 'memes' and allowing access to accounts that users have created.

Images created are for the use of the creator/s of the image, if designated 'private'.

We do not share any information collected with external / third parties.

### Cookies

Cookies are used on this site to track usage and to record content ('memes') that you may create. They may also be used to assist in presenting the site to a logged in user. 

Cookies may also be set in your browser by third-party tracking or ad services, for the purposes of statistical analysis or to better target promotional material. 

### Changes to This Privacy Statement

We may occasionally update this privacy statement. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.
